http://www.cellpex.com/privacy-policy

Announcements
(23)
Industry News
(2704)
Trade Voices
(2263)
Contributors
Support
(9)
Archive
(4925)
June 2020
(2)
May 2020
(8)
April 2020
(12)
March 2020
(12)
February 2020
(11)
January 2020
(7)
December 2019
(9)
November 2019
(16)
October 2019
(10)
September 2019
(18)
August 2019
(17)
July 2019
(17)
June 2019
(23)
May 2019
(24)
April 2019
(30)
March 2019
(12)
February 2019
(27)
January 2019
(34)
December 2018
(31)
November 2018
(33)
October 2018
(23)
September 2018
(13)
August 2018
(12)
July 2018
(18)
June 2018
(22)
May 2018
(25)
April 2018
(25)
March 2018
(16)
February 2018
(12)
January 2018
(50)
December 2017
(18)
November 2017
(37)
October 2017
(19)
September 2017
(44)
August 2017
(26)
July 2017
(32)
June 2017
(49)
May 2017
(33)
April 2017
(44)
March 2017
(94)
February 2017
(46)
January 2017
(38)
December 2016
(29)
November 2016
(25)
October 2016
(37)
September 2016
(36)
August 2016
(29)
July 2016
(32)
June 2016
(38)
May 2016
(33)
April 2016
(26)
March 2016
(38)
February 2016
(26)
January 2016
(40)
December 2015
(45)
November 2015
(40)
October 2015
(46)
September 2015
(27)
August 2015
(35)
July 2015
(30)
June 2015
(42)
May 2015
(37)
April 2015
(52)
March 2015
(62)
February 2015
(44)
January 2015
(53)
December 2014
(50)
November 2014
(63)
October 2014
(56)
September 2014
(66)
August 2014
(63)
July 2014
(58)
June 2014
(53)
May 2014
(64)
April 2014
(45)
March 2014
(34)
February 2014
(54)
January 2014
(34)
December 2013
(19)
November 2013
(20)
October 2013
(17)
September 2013
(44)
August 2013
(29)
July 2013
(34)
June 2013
(9)
May 2013
(18)
April 2013
(21)
March 2013
(31)
February 2013
(9)
January 2013
(51)
December 2012
(36)
November 2012
(37)
October 2012
(29)
September 2012
(46)
August 2012
(32)
July 2012
(44)
June 2012
(42)
May 2012
(45)
April 2012
(39)
March 2012
(54)
February 2012
(62)
January 2012
(58)
December 2011
(22)
November 2011
(21)
October 2011
(45)
September 2011
(23)
August 2011
(41)
July 2011
(36)
June 2011
(38)
May 2011
(34)
April 2011
(21)
March 2011
(35)
February 2011
(73)
January 2011
(64)
December 2010
(57)
November 2010
(34)
October 2010
(65)
September 2010
(58)
August 2010
(27)
July 2010
(79)
June 2010
(55)
May 2010
(39)
April 2010
(30)
March 2010
(24)
February 2010
(34)
January 2010
(19)
December 2009
(17)
November 2009
(25)
October 2009
(30)
September 2009
(17)
August 2009
(16)
July 2009
(10)
June 2009
(16)
May 2009
(11)
April 2009
(46)
March 2009
(16)
February 2009
(19)
January 2009
(25)
December 2008
(2)
October 2008
(1)
June 2008
(3)
May 2008
(1)
December 2007
(3)
November 2007
(3)
July 2007
(1)
March 2007
(1)
November 2006
(1)
August 2006
(2)
July 2006
(2)
January 2006
(1)
September 2005
(2)
cell phones wholesale 0.65
Privacy Policy
New Post
Apr 01, 2018
(Updated Dec 09, 2020)
Cellpex,
United States,
Ohio
-
admin
We consider and respect any individual's privacy seriously and importantly. The fundamental purpose of the services that Cellpex.com provides you; for example, Offerboard enabling exchanges of trade leads, offers and inquiries, listing through the Cellpex.com and search engines, etc., requires that we gather, process, use and distribute the member's information which also you provide directly; for example, your company name, contact information, and homepage, etc. Therefore, Cellpex.com does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. If you wish to remove your company or update your company's information, please Contact Us.
Information Collection and Use
As registering for the services provided on our website, you would be required to provide valid information including your name, company name, address, contact numbers and further personal information. We will use this information in providing services that you request, and letting you know of available services that give values to you and fit your business. We may also use this information to customize the contents for your convenience in using our website. Furthermore, Cellpex.com estimates and collects statistical Data about Cellpex.com sites and users, such as IP address, browsers, pages viewed, and number of users etc. However, as doing so Cellpex.com may not grant any individual name, email address or any other information related to the privacy concern to any users. We can use this data for improvement of Cellpex.com content quality upon customer or market tendency, behavior, and trends. We may provide this statistical information to third parties without any exposure of private personal information and any notice to the provider.
Registration
In order to become a member at Cellpex.com, an applicant must firstly complete the registration form with honesty and sincerity. While registering, the applicant is required to give their current and valid contact information, along with their company's profile. This information will be exposed on Cellpex.com Company Directory and more relevant services at Cellpex.com exclusively for the benefits of his/her trade business and for enhancing Cellpex.com contents. Cellpex.com does reserve the rights to use the company information provided by our users and any other information resulted posting at Cellpex.com, into any form that Cellpex.com sees it fits in. It is optional for a user to provide demographic information (such as gender, title and country). All the user information shall be provided to banking merchants to enable transactions to take place and to allow us to determine the credit-worthiness of our users.
Partnerships & Relationships in Affiliation
We have established relationships or partnerships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services that Cellpex.com may not contain. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our website, or through banners and letter mails in which both ourselves and these other parties (or partners) share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. The Privacy Policy of such other parties may differ from ours. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding of any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.
Cookies
Like most websites, Cellpex.com uses cookies to store a member's profile. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the User. Usage of a cookie is taken place in no way linked to any personal private information while logging in our site. Once the member closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If the user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site, but access to some functions can be denied. Cellpex.com does not use cookies to track a member's Internet viewing habits or for marketing purposes.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to obtain metrics, analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. In addition, your trade leads and contact information will be available to trade lead search engines from other web sites. Please be aware that Cellpex.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the Privacy Policy of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. We employ all the latest technology in firewalls and the servers that we store our information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage at a hosting company. If you have any questions about the security at our website contact us.
Correcting Your Information
You can access the information that we collect online and maintain through normal updating methods. To update, correct or delete this information, you can go to User Profile.
Site and Service Updates
We periodically send announcement on site and service to Members. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about upgrades and changes to service. We communicate with the members to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. Users of our site will be informed when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this in purpose that our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will update this posting so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Therefore, you should check up on this Privacy Policy regularly.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, feel free to Contact Us.
© 2011 Cellpex LLC, Ohio, USA. Designated trademarks and brands are the property of their respective owners.
Use of this Web site constitutes acceptance of Cellpex User Agreement, Product Listing Policy and Privacy Policy.
